And tell me,
hello guys welcome back to my YouTube
channel this morning today I will show you a video of
this new model of Bajaj Pulsar NS 160 UBS which has been
launched in Bajaj so
guys if it was damaged then there will be an
insurance claim for it so what parts are
changed I will show you clearly later so
guys first look at the damage in the phone,
its entire setup
of the instrument has died so its indicators etc have been
damaged, if so
you can see what is on it and if you
look at the back its indicator has been
damaged here so all these things have got
interest on this thing so these plans do this
how to do it
I will tell you everything in this video
I will show you all the things which have been activated
so you can see its
pass etc. whatever these things have changed then there will be such an
insurance claim so first guys I will
show you the Waju NS 160 so
all the things which have been damaged
When did the accident happen, everything has been opened here, so
after opening, this photo will be sent to a company, so
this thing
of the bike which has been damaged, then this thing will be used for
insurance claim, so guys, if you
can see that everything has been opened,
everything will be fine, so guys, I am giving you
some notice directly about its settings, so guys,
see the from car,
its sugar etc. which was updated, has been
installed here, so you
can see that its from car which is like this, the
entire set of social has changed, so
you can see its front option bar, the
set of NS 160 after 200th, the
entire set, so what is its price, I will
tell you everything later, what is its
price or not,
so guys, see the change class of the phone which has changed here,
and the latest number of this channel, then the
style of normal will also change, so what is its price,
I will show you, so its
partner JE 2328  Its price is
more than 200, so there will be changes like this too, so if it
starts here, then I will show you all these
details, so it is being installed here,
its number plate is bus stand,
so it was closed in the system,
after this actress, this has also changed, so
this insurance claim will not come, it will
come in this letter, that is why the change is happening here
and if I show you an important
thing here, its health lamp which is NS
160 exam, its price is
₹5 in 2009, so I am showing it to you people after
unboxing it, so you people
see its model, when it
comes to Hitler, there is a valve inside the lamp,
so leaving aside the exam,
I will definitely show it to you, you should
see it after some time, test it, then
you people will come to know and how is it actually, it takes a
hit from the company, so
leaving aside the hair, Hitler only goes to sleep, and
one more thing is there, the
glam marks remain on the side, the
marks of hat are returned and from both the sides
I take the pen drive, this thing will change,
so its indicator
light will change, so what is its price, I will
show you later in the middle and
one more thing, guys, its headlamp, okay,
so you guys can see the hair lock marks from the side,
so this mark will also change, so
what is its price, I will
show you later, so guys, first of all, what I have
shown you is its head lock site marks,
okay, on the side, 100 ODI career is
starting, so guys, before this,
you will
not get this thing set separately, okay, one cup of water
comes in it, so all these things will have to be purchased
and in case of infection, all these things will be provided by the
company, okay, so guys, it is being
extracted and installed here, so
you can see that here, the indicator
site marks and the glasses are torn and very
soon, here the history is being done, so
after the total is installed in,
I will show you how the extra
looks like, MS Word 168 loop, so guys, let me
tell you all these things  If
I show you the safe change exam, then
what is its actual name, I will show you
in the packet and I will also show you its price, so
its bracket drop is its price in the
notification, so you
can see it for a moment, which is a New Orleans,
so the first one is joke, so this
change also has 10 top bracket
written on it, so its price is to dowry
market high Lord Shiva 1237, so
you will find it in this photo, which
is an aggregator and see its setup is
complete, which is its health loop,
so Hitler has fight mark and hate hate love
mark and its kilo selling has become
sufficient and its indicator has also become
historic, so guys, like
insulin does, the taste of doing will be restaurant, so
after that I will show you
how the total does not go the same, so
guys, I am telling you one more thing, so
its name is Swan Stuart Meeker  If the
meter here is not damaged then this is the old one
which was shattered earlier then it will
come in here so next here will be
Pragjyotish which I had shown you earlier, if this is
insulin
then the meter should be done, that is why it is done to
support the meter, so how and let me
show you one more thing, I will show you its gel change, so
its market
meaning, the same seal which is taken by MS Word from the
language, there has been a change in the top,
side effects and share tax, Hitler
Nuskhe, the indicator has also changed, so
I will show you those and other things, so
its leg is okay, two
pilots have also changed from the company, I will show you near it, so
click on every word loop front on this side, then its
price will
change from this, then the cash withdrawal key will change, its
handlebar has changed, so
its price is dowry which
you get at a very cheap price,
MS Word Sikha Studio which is
available at a very cheap price, so here
and there will be a change whose class was  So if there will be a
change then you get one payment from the arrest of the app in
2004 in this powder, so
look at the gas, that is, the
setup of Hitler of Afghan, the Hitler, which I
showed you first, here I am becoming a historian, so its
mind is complete on slaughter, that is, let me talk about the
accident that happened, it had
not been a week since the accident, that is, the
points episode of the from has been on flame
till now, this thing is glamorous, so an
insurance claim has been made on this thing
[music]
So Hitler has been installed here at many places, so the
vehicle is complete, that is, NS 160 is well
completed, all its crop
insurance scheme work has been completed,
so you can feel that all the
work of this from, all the broken
stuff, everything has been changed, so its
Hitler mod on thankfully has been changed, so
you people in this and I will show you once more,
this has changed, so you people
can see that this stuff which was damaged is of
extension  If it happens then all those things have been
replaced for the customer, that means he has got the lines
club, money and things have changed, so
I will show you what is the total bill of this,
you please take a look at the bill once, pay
attention, only one thing has changed, so guys
please do not look at it, he has got a total of ₹16
thousand ₹70, so here the name of all the items is here,
okay, its Bhadesar MRP price, everything
is there, okay, so you guys take a
screenshot, you will get to know
which mantra is what price, so
you just take a screenshot, today's video ends here
and the next video is coming soon, if you like the
video then please like it
and when I subscribe to you,
subscribe quickly and
you can also follow me on Instagram,
I will give the link here in the description box,
as you please
fold once, so till then bye see you get it for you